You okay, Bill?
你还好吗   比尔
Are you kidding?
开什么玩笑
I'm great.
棒极了
Can we do that again?
能再来一次吗
Huh? Are you sure?
啊  你确定吗
Then, yeah! Come on!
那么   好呀 来吧
You did it, Bill! You did it!
比尔   你做到了 你做到了
Dad, did you see?
爸爸   你看到了吗
I did.
我看到了
You're definitely a chip off the old tusk.
真是虎父无犬子啊
Can we go to the sky gazer platform now?
现在我们能去观天台吗
Wow!
哇
It's tusk-tastic!
太美了
Tuskerrific!
太不可思议了
-It's...   -wow!
-哇   -真是太赞了
Yeah! It's wow!
是的   太赞了
So my pappy is the only other elephant to ever see this?
所以除了我   我祖父是唯一看过这些景色的大象喽
The sky gazer platform wasn't here back then.
那时还没有这个观天台呢
You've climbed even higher than your grandfather, Badou.
你比你祖父爬得还高   巴豆
Thanks, Chickpea.
谢谢你   启库
I'm really glad I got to see it.
能看到这些   真得太开心了
Together.
我也是